Destiny. Fate. Dreams.
These unstoppable ideals are
held deep in the heart of man.
As long as there are people
who seek freedom in this life,
these things shall not
vanish from the earth.
People tell me my head's in the clouds.
I don't care what they say
because I'm dreaming of you.
You are the treasure I found.
So bright, so bold, and so elusive.
It's hard to look away.
Even though it's blinding me.
There are no words to
describe how I feel inside.
I'm really, really stuck on you.
I have to follow my dreams,
however crazy they seem.
And I won't stop till I
get there, you will see.
You're all I need to have
the strength to believe.
Believe in wonderland.
I'm gonna follow my dreams,
however crazy they seem.
I'm gonna share them
with you, a love so true.
You're all I want,
together we can move on.
We live how we want to.
There is no limit to us.
We have the power of love.
We don't want to live ordinary lives.
We have a chance to live in paradise.
We live in wonderland.
Hey, quit slacking on! Ouch!
Hey, chore boys, wash the windows
when you're finished here.
Sir!
One, two, three, four.
One, two.
Uh, I can't stand this.
Kobe can be the model chore boy if
he wants, but why do I have to do it?
Damn it,
if it weren't for that stupid Straw Hat
guy, none of this would have happened?
It's all his fault,
it's because of that straw
hat guy that I'm here
doing stupid chores instead
of living the good life!
Hey, Hellnipo?
What do you want?
Why are you touching me like that?
You shouldn't blame
everything on Luffy like that,
it isn't his fault, he was
just doing the right thing.
For a long time you could use your
father's power to get through life.
Things are different now.
We've got to work long and hard on
our own to accomplish our dreams.
Oh, please.
You know my dream?
Someday I'm going to be a
great officer in the Marines.
I'll chase bad guys and defend justice.
How stupid can you be?
A wimp like you becoming a
Marine officer like my dad?
No way that will ever happen.
I know that it will.
Thanks to Luffy, I know that
I can do anything that I want.
That's right!
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!
I decided that long ago, and if I
die fighting for it, it's alright!
So I decided to be like
Luffy and do anything,
even risk my life, to
achieve my final goal!
Well, now we can work hard
and reach our goals together!
Get it!
You think I'm going to listen to this?
What the heck makes you think
you can tell me what I should do?
And what could you have possibly learned
from that pathetic excuse for a pirate?
Don't talk about Luffy like that!
I haven't done anything
but try to help you out!
I don't remember asking for your help!
Help that fool, will you please?
Stop acting foolish!
Oh, please, you're calling me a fool?
Take that!
Would you stop coming?
I've got some more!
What's going on here?
We're sorry, sir!
Really?
That explosion earlier was from you guys?
They didn't kick you out of
the Marines, did they, Kobe?
Thank you, ma 'am.
No, they actually allowed
us to stay enlisted.
Yeah, but we had to agree to
work for free for 50 years.
Getting kicked out would
have been so much better.
Attention!
I will now inform you about
the nature of our mission.
What do you want?
It's my dad!
Captain Morgan is being sent to Marine
Headquarters to face a court-martial for
the crimes of military
exploitation and the
cruel and unusual treatment of civilians.
Our mission is to transfer the
prisoner to Vice Admiral Garden.
Reckless lowlife bums!
You have no right to defy my superiority!
I am Marine Captain Axe Han Morgan!
So I guess it's really going to happen.
I mean, I know that he deserves to
get court-martialed and all of that.
I get it, given the stuff that he did.
But honestly, even after all
that, I still respected him.
Damn it!
Why?
Kobe, do you think that
they're going to execute him?
I don't know.
I guess I should probably be ready for
something like that to happen, huh?
But he's my dad.
Oh, no.
Marines!
All hands on deck!
Fall in!
It's Vice Admiral Gar...
So that's Marine Vice Admiral
Garp, the man they call the Fist.
He's a great hero of the seas who
travels all over the Grand Line.
Vice Admiral Garp, thank
you for coming all this way.
We are pleased to deliver
Captain Morgan to you.
I heard you.
I'm a bit tired because I've
been up for five days now.
You are indeed a dedicated marine, sir.
No, I've been trying to set a record for
the most donuts eaten in a single sitting.
Sir?
The sugar kept me going at first,
but I've been at it for a while now,
and I guess the lack of sleep
is starting to get to me.
Old man, cut the sleeping act already
No one move!
If anyone moves a muscle, I'll hack this
chore boy up And feed him to the sharks!
But, Daddy, why are you doing this?
Sir, please stop this!
Remember who is your son?
How can you do something like that to him?
My son?
What do I need with a son?
What I want now is freedom.
I don't care about his life.
I'll cut him into a thousand
pieces if I have to.
But... Daddy!
Help me!
Somebody help me, please!
Good riddance, you fools!
Ready the cannon.
Load the cannon! Take game!
Target, 16 degrees starboard.
Distance, 8263. Now, ready?
No!
Please, just wait!
I'm begging you not to shoot! Please stop!
He has a hostage on that boat! Move it!
I won't!
In that case, you're dead.
Maybe so, but at least I won't be
guilty of abandoning my friends!
Please, I can fix this!
I'll capture Morgan myself!
Come back! You idiot!
You'll never be able to
capture him by yourself!
Let's let him try.
He's either brave and dumb, or just dumb.
What do we do?
All right, I'm awake again.
Now, what's all this noise about?
Vice Admiral Garp, you're alive.
I was certain that monster had killed you.
What?
One of the men has been killed?
I can't believe I slept
through something like that.
Who was it?
Oh, right.
Free at last!
Just you watch.
The world will be kneeling
at my feet again in no time.
I will rule the seas.
The world will quake in terror.
Now set our course to the west, boy.
What are you doing?
I said set our course.
No!
Huh?
I won't have any part in your plans.
Kuma put everything on the
line trying to save me.
He even risked getting kicked out of the
Marines to help me, and they're his dream.
He fights for what he believes in
no matter what, and so could I.
Dad, I'm going to capture you.
You might as well just give up.
What do you think you're doing, brat?
Are you too stupid to know
what you're up against, huh?
What can a useless piece of
scum like you hope to do to me?
Damn it.
It's time you learned your
place, you pathetic insect.
No, I'm not listening to you anymore.
From now on, I'm the one who's
going to decide how to live my life.
Stop being such an idiot.
What could someone like you possibly do?
He can do whatever he wants.
You came!
Stop right there, Morgan!
You two are absolutely pathetic.
How can a couple of pitiful insects like
you expect to capture someone like me?
If you even think about getting
in my way, I'll kill you both!
Thank you for coming to save me.
I'm sorry it turned out like this.
I'm glad I came.
Aren't we friends after all?
Oh, um, Koby.
You little pests aren't worth the
time it would take to kill you.
I'd better never see your faces again.
Morgan!
I may have let you sail
away from me alive today,
but someday I'm going to
catch you, I promise you that!
Do you hear me?
Someday I'm going to capture you!
Just you, wait!
Please forgive my poor supervision, sir.
Allowing the prisoner to
escape was inexcusable.
We're very sorry to you, sir!
After today, these two will be
kicked out of the Marines for good.
The two of you are truly lost causes.
I don't know anyone who
would take you in now.
But turning you loose would
only burden the public.
I have no choice but to take you
with me to Marine headquarters.
What, Vice Admiral?
Sir, you're actually going to take these
two chore boys with you to headquarters?
Is that a problem?
Of course not.
No problem here, sir.
And do you two have a problem?
If you want to run away,
this is your last chance.
Not that I'd allow you to
get very far, of course.
Well now, this certainly
has been an interesting day.
What?
Marine headquarters?
Yeah.
Vice Admiral Garp can be
very unpredictable at times.
He's pretty high up on the
food chain though, right?
Yes, very high up.
Then those two must have been very promising
to have caught his attention like that.
Stupid, stupid, stupid, stupid, stupid!
Why did you let them go
without saying goodbye, stupid?
I still wanted to play
with them some more.
And I wanted to talk to them more.
I was even learning how to cook.
I wanted to make them a yummy lunch next
time they came over, but now I can't.
I didn't even get to say
goodbye before they left.
Why did they have to leave?
I'm sorry.
Please forgive me.
Rick, that's enough.
Leave him alone now, dear.
You don't have to be so sad.
They'll come back after they've
become fine marine officers.
What good is this?
How are we supposed to become
marines by mopping floors?
Did you ever think that maybe this
is just a hobby that old geezer has?
A hobby?
Yeah,
a new hobby called tormenting
poor chore boys just for fun I'm
telling you the old man's crazy
enough that it might be true.
Think about it for a sec.
Would you bird stop chiming?
I love you.